Contact

kennedy.danko@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/kennedy-danko-349b29181 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Volunteering

Leadership

Training

Certifications

Advanced Cardiovascular Life Support Experienced Provider (ACLS)

CPR & AED

Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS)

Registered Nurse

Honors-Awards

Magna Cum Laude Sigma Theta Tau Affiliated

Kennedy Danko

Registered Nurse with a Bachelors in Science of Nursing Greater Los Angeles Area

Summary

Experienced Food and Beverage Server with a demonstrated history of working in the restaurants industry. Skilled in Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS), Volunteering, Time Management, Leadership, and Skilled Multitasker. Strong operations professional with a Bachelor of nursing focused in Student from West Coast University.

Experience

Temecula Valley Hospital Registered Nurse June 2020 - Present (2 months)

Yard House Restaurants Food and Beverage Server January 2015 - June 2020 (5 years 6 months) Riverside

I was hired as a food expediter in 2015 where I worked with the kitchen and staff to ensure food was plated and staged correctly before reaching the tables. After six months, I became a trainer to train all staff being hired in positions of food expediter, server, and host. In 2017 I was then promoted to server. As a server, I wait tables, make sure guest are happy, and anticipate their needs.

Education

West Coast University

Bachelors of Science in Nursing- BSN, Student · (2018 - 2020)